

Denys Zubko

Automation QA Engineer

Seattle, USA +1(360) 660-76-76 · zubko.denys@gmail.com

site portfolio

Skills
TypeScript
Java
Java
HTML & CSS
SQL
Git
Playwright
Selenium
Postman
Jmeter
Jira & TestRail
Languages
English
Ukranian
Russian
German

Profile

Experienced Automation QA Engineer with a six-year experience, adept in both automated and manual testing strategies. Accomplished in leading small QA teams to significantly improve product quality and accelerate delivery timelines through effective testing solutions. Actively involved in enhancing processes to boost software reliability and operational efficiency.

Employment History

Automation QA Engineer, Avenga

January 2022 — Present

In this role I collaborated on several projects (see the list of projects <u>here</u>), leveraging my skills as a software engineer in test. My primary responsibilities included implementing and executing a diverse range of testing strategies, such as API testing, e2e testing, load testing, and database testing.

Hybrid Automation & Manual QA, Patron Empowerment

February 2019 — January 2022

In this role I was responsible for leading small QA teams (up to 5 people), overseeing both manual and automated testing processes. Ensure high software quality, streamline workflows, and extending automation coverage to optimize testing efficiency.

Education

National Aerospace University <Kharkiv Aviation Institute>

2019 - 2021

Master's degree, Mobile application engineering

National Aerospace University <Kharkiv Aviation Institute>

2015 - 2019

Bachelor's degree, Systems Engineering